in less than a second the blast leveled
the city's Center and vaporized 35,000
people while more powerful than the
bomit Hiroshima much more of the city
would manage to survive as the hills
surrounding the point of the explosion
mitigated the effects of the resulting
Shockwave and Fireball even so tens of
thousands more would later die as a
direct result of their injuries or the
effects of radiation in total the atomic
bombs dropped on Hiroshima and Nagasaki
would claim over 200,000 lives with the
two cities being wiped out in the blink
of an eye it was a scale of Destruction
never before seen in history with a
single bomb able to eviscerate an entire
city within seconds the world would now
wait to hear Japan's response would
their government still remain silent
would they watch on as more cities even
Tokyo itself was wiped from the face of
the Earth just what would it take for
the Japanese to surrender no